farmersonly.com 2013-12-20

# FarmersOnly.com - Privacy Policy

The last update to our Privacy Policy was posted on May 13, 2013. This Privacy Policy governs the privacy terms of our website, www.FarmersOnly.com (Website), as well as the Service we provide through it.

**_Definitions_**

"Non Personal Information" is information that is not personally identifiable to you and we automatically collect when you access our Website with a web browser.

"Personally Identifiable Information" is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained in order for us to provide you with products and services. Personally Identifiable Information may include information such as your name, address, phone number, email address, credit card information, and other related information that you provide to us or that we obtain about you.

The terms "us" or "we" or "our" refers to **Farmersonly Media Inc.,** the owner of this Website.

A "Member" is someone who has registered with our Website to use our Service. A Member can create a "Profile", which is an online representation of Personally Identifiable Information regarding that Member.

"Service" refers to the service we provide through our Website to our Members.

A "Visitor" is someone who browses our Website, but hasn't become a Member.

A "User" is a collective identifier that refers to either a Visitor or a Member.

All text, information, graphics, audio, video, and data offered through our Website, whether free to all or part of our paid Service, whether originating from us or from our Users, are collectively known as our "Content". We may also refer to any Content uploaded by our Members to their respective Profiles as "Member Content". Any reference to our Website/Service, also includes our Content by reference.

**_Your Privacy and What Our Privacy Policy Covers_**

**Farmersonly Media Inc.** is committed to your privacy and takes it very seriously. Our Privacy Policy tells you what Personally Identifiable Information **Farmersonly Media Inc.** may collect from you, how we may share your Personally Identifiable Information, and how you can limit our sharing of your Personally Identifiable Information. **Farmersonly Media Inc.** is committed to providing an exemplary online experience as well as securing the privacy of all our users. **Farmersonly Media Inc.** and any of our affiliates respect your privacy and recognize the need for appropriate protection and management of your Personally Identifiable Information as you share with us.

**_Information Collected_**

Generally, you control the amount of information you provide to **Farmersonly Media Inc.** when you use our Website/Service. Visitors provide mostly Non Personal Information whereas Members will obviously provide more information, including Personally Identifiable Information. Please note that any information you provide at registration or in your Profile may be used by **Farmersonly Media Inc.** as described in this Privacy Policy.

When you become a Member, you will be required to provide Personally Indentifiable Information to **Farmersonly Media Inc.** in order for us to provide our Service. If you have any hesitation about providing information to us and/or having your information displayed on our Website or otherwise used in any manner as permitted in this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Service, you should not become a Member or close your account if already a Member. 

We collect your personal information in the following ways:

**At Registration**

In order to become a Member, you must register with our Website. You must provide some basic Personally Identifiable Information such as name and email address in order to register.

**Profile Information**

Once you become a Member, you may provide additional Personally Identifiable Information such as your picture, personal interests, and other related information. Providing any additional Personally Identifiable Information is entirely your choice. However, the more such information your provide, the more benefit you will receive from our Service.

**Customer Service**

We may collect Personally Identifiable Information when you contact us for customer service issues or when we need to investigate complaints against you or violations of our Terms of Service. 

**Online Forms and Information Requests**

Generally, we collect site usage information from any User of our Website when you fill out forms or request information from us. 

**Cookies**

Like most websites, our Website may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of our site you have visited, so the next time you visit the site, we can better personalize the content that you see on our Website. Most browser software can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to use certain functionality on our Website correctly or at all. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.

**Web Beacons**

We may also use web beacons to collect Non Personal Information about your use of our Website as well as those of our affiliates, and your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information we collect by Web Beacons allows us to statistically monitor the number of people that open our emails and why they opened our emails. Our Web Beacons are not used to track your activity outside of our Website or those of our affiliates. We do not link Non Personal Information from Web Beacons to Personally Identifiable Information without your permission.

**Automatic Information**

When you visit our Website, we automatically receive certain types of Non Personal Information. This can include the URL of the website from which you entered our Website. We also receive the website to which you're headed when you leave our Website. We also receivethe IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet service provider name, web browser type, and computer operating system. We use all of this this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website/Service.

**_How We Use Your Information_**

**Farmersonly Media Inc.** uses the Personally Identifiable Information that you provide for provide the Service to you and as provided below:

#### Website Communications

When **Farmersonly Media Inc.** communicates with you about our Website/Service, we may use the email address you provided on your Profile and/or send messages through the messaging features associated with our Service. We may also send you emails/messages to inform you about changes or service messages regarding our Website/Service. Finally, we may also send you emails/messages with promotional information about **Farmersonly Media Inc.** or our affiliates, unless you have opted out of receiving such information. You can change contact preferences at any time through your Profile settings. While you can opt-out of promotional messages, you cannot opt-out of receiving service messages.

#### Member Communications

When you communicate with other Members using the Service, you control the Personally Identifiable Information that is transmitted to such Members. If part of your communication involves an email to another Member, your email address will be exposed to that Member.

#### Customizing Our Content

**Farmersonly Media Inc.** uses the information you provide to us to customize your experience on our Website/Service.

#### Sharing Information with Affiliates and Other Third Parties

**Farmersonly Media Inc.** does not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes. We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to affiliates that provide services to Farmersonly Media Inc. with regards to our Website/Service (i.e. payment processors, website hosting companies, etc.); such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the respective services and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use of such information.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information,browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

#### External Search Engines

Also, any portions of your Profile that you make publically viewable may be spidered by search engines. Even if you later restrict access to such information, these search engines may have cached copies of the information you once allowed to be seen publically. 

#### Contests, Surveys, and Polls

**Farmersonly Media Inc.** or its Members (through their Profile), may conduct online Contests, Surveys, and Polls (collectively, "Participation Events") through our Website/Service. These Participation Events may ask you to provide Personally Identifiable Information. It is strictly _your_ choice to participate in such Participation Events and whether you choose to provide Personally Identifiable Information.

#### Member Search Functions

Our Service has search functions that allow Members to search for other Members. Such search functions will be strictly limited to searching on publically viewable information from Member Profiles. 

#### Public Postings

Our Service allows for Users to post public messagess offers message board functions through its Service to allow Members to post public messages. If you post on public message boards, please use care when exposing any Personally Identifiable Information as such information is not protected by our Privacy Policy nor are we liable should you choose to disclose Personally Identifiable Information through Public Postings. 

#### Testimonials

Should you provide **Farmersonly Media Inc.** with a testimonial with regards to our Website/Service, you are authorizing **Farmersonly Media Inc.'s** use of such testimonial in public displays in any form to third parties, whether Users of our Website/Service, including, but not limited to postings on our Website/Service, emails to prospective or current Members, and web ads placed on other websites. If you provide a testimonial, please use care when exposing any Personally Identifiable Information as such information is not protected by our Privacy Policy nor are we liable should you choose to disclose Personally Identifiable Information through Testimonials.

#### Legally Required Releases of Information

**Farmersonly Media Inc.** may have need to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information information, if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process; (b) necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our Terms of Service; (d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties including you and/or other Members; and/or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of **Farmersonly Media Inc.** , our Users, employees, and affiliates. 

#### Disclosures to Successors

If **Farmersonly Media Inc.** was acquired or merged, in whole or in part, to another entity that would become responsible for providing the Service to you, we would have the right to transfer your Personally Identiable Information to such entity and that entity would have the right to use your Personally Identifiable Information according to the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as to any changes to this Privacy Policy as instituted by such entity.

**_Opting Out of Sharing Information_**

**Farmersonly Media Inc.** provides you with the ability to opt-out of future unaffiliated third-party disclosures of your Personally Identifiable Information. Such opt-out will not affect disclosures otherwise permitted by law including but not limited to: (a) disclosures to affiliates; (b) disclosures to third-party service providers who provide certain services for our business, such as credit card processing, computer system services, shipping, data management, or promotional services; (c) disclosures to third parties as necessary to fulfill your requests; (d) disclosures to governmental agencies or law enforcement departments or otherwise required to be made under applicable law; (e) previously completed disclosures to third parties; or (f) disclosures Participation Events in which you choose to participate.

**_Changing Your Information_**

You may change your Personally Identifiable Information at any time using facilities found on our Website, including removing yourself from mailing lists. If at any time you need assistance, just send us an email or customer service request form with your request.

**_Protecting Your Child's Privacy_**

We follow United States laws regarding the protection of children's privacy. Our Service is not designed for use by anyone under the age of 18 (Child). We do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from a Child; however, you acknowledge that we cannot accurately verify the age of our Users nor do we have any liability to do so. If you are parent or legal guardian who suspects their Child is attempting to use our Website/Service, please contact us immediately if you wish to remove your Child's information. We may ask you to provide identification to confirm that you are indeed the child's parent or legal guardian. If you are a Child, please do not attempt to use our Website/Service unless you have your parent's permission.

**_Links to Other Websites_**

Our Website/Service will likely contain links to other websites. **Farmersonly Media Inc.** has no control of such websites and you agree that these websites are not under our control and are not subject to our Privacy Policy. These websites will likely have their own privacy policies. We have no responsibility for these websites and provide links to these websites solely for your convenience. You acknowledge that your use and access of these websites is solely at your own risk. It is your responsibility to check the privacy policies and other legal documents of these websites to see how they treat your personal information.

**_Our Email Policy_**

**Farmersonly Media Inc.** and our affiliates fully comply with United States laws regarding SPAM email. You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from **Farmersonly Media Inc.** and our affiliates. We agree that we will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission. It is very important that you understand that email is not considered a secure form of communication. As such, please take care in what you disclose in any email that you send to us.

**_Our Security Policy_**

**Farmersonly Media Inc.** has constructed our Website/Service using industry standard encryption and authentication tools to protect your Personally Identifiable Information. When we collect your Personally Identifiable Information through our Website/Service, we encrypt this information and attempt to prevent unauthorized access to it by using industry standard technologies, such as encryption software, routers and firewalls. Unfortunately, due to the nature of the Internet, we cannot completely guarantee that your Personally Identifiable Information is completely protected. We strongly urge you to protect any password you may have for our Service and not share it with anyone. You should always log out of our Service when not in use, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a public computer.

**_Payment Sources_**

You will have to provide a credit card or other payment source to use our Service. We use third-party billing services and HAVE NO CONTROL over these services. While **Farmersonly Media Inc.** will use commercially reasonable efforts to protect against unauthorized use of your payment source information, you understand and agree that we are in no way responsible for any misuse of your payment source information.

**_Privacy Policy Updates_**

**Farmersonly Media Inc.** reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. We will also change the "Last Updated" date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies.

**_Questions About Our Privacy Practices or This Privacy Policy_**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Practices or this Policy, please email us at [privacy@FarmersOnly.com](mailto:privacy@FarmersOnly.com).
